# ROBERTO ROMERO MARTÍN

# JUNIOR DEVELOPER

### EDUCATION

#### **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER**

Level 4 by QA
Oct 2022 - Jan 2023

# DEVELOPMENT OF WEB APPLICATIONS

Diploma of Higher Education Ilerna
Online

Jan 2020- Jan 2022

# ENGLISH, LANGUAGE AND CULTURE

Degree UNED Jan 2016- Jan 2020

# PROFILE

I am currently searching for a role as a web developer, after two years I completed my BTEC Diploma in IT "Development of Web Applications". I had a six-month apprenticeship where I learnt how to create websites from scratch using mainly CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and React.

I have just finished "Software Developer Level 4" with QA, learning technologies such as Azure, Python and MySQL. At the same time, I keep building Apps to improve my knowledge of the above-mentioned technologies and learning some new ones.

# PERSONAL DETAILS

+447867060691

York, England

https://roberromero.github.io/my-portafolio/

in www.linkedin.com/in/roberto-romero-martin

Settled status

# EXPERIENCE

# OXYGEN WORKSPACE Madrid, Spain

Jan 2022 - Jun 2022

- Creating websites using: HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React.
- Working with Programmers and Web Designers to create a website that matches the visual design intent under the supervision of a CTO.
- Communicating with business colleagues to gather and refine requirements and specifications for content development within agreed-upon timelines. Git, GitHub and Slack were used.
- Agile Scrum Methodology was used.

#### OJALÁ SPANISH ACADEMY

https://ojala-spanishacademy.co.uk/ York, England

Mar 2012 - Present

- Delivered one-to-one and group teachings, maintaining student engagement and enthusiasm through subject passion and effective communication.
- Planned and executed innovative lessons to improve students reading, writing, speaking and understanding skills through different techniques.

### SKILLS

#### HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript

I had a six-month apprenticeship where I learnt how to create websites from a Figma design using HTML, CSS, and Vanilla JavaScript.

#### **React and Vue**

In my apprenticeship I also had the opportunity to work with React and Vue in other projects.

#### Git and GitHub

Experience working in small groups using these two tools.

#### PHP and Laravel

During my BTEC Diploma I created some projects.

#### MySQL and XAMPP

During my BTEC Diploma I created databases and projects.

I also practised MySQL during my bootcamp at QA "Software Developer Level 4".

# SOFT SKILLS

Teamwork

Problem-Solving

Communication

Adaptability

Ability to listen

Creativity

### EXPERIENCE

# HERMES LOGISTIC - ACCIONA - LOGISTIC OPERATIONS MANAGER

Madrid, Spain

Aug 2006 - Jan 2012

- Supervised all facets of routine deliveries by effectively routing loads, managing drivers and meeting DFT requirements.
- Maintained workplace safety by involving employees in order to maximize engagement to team morale.
- Ensure staff followed administrative policies and compliance regulations by closely monitoring daily operations and performing safety audits.

### REFERENCES

Availability upon request.

# HOBBIES AND

I like spending time with my family, learning new skills, cooking, traveling and meeting new people.

# OTHER INFO

Spanish is my first language, but I am also fluent in English.

I have my own car and I am happy to commute and open to new challenges that could involve living in another place.

I would need a two-week notice to start in my new position.



